(Shopkeeper:)- You?
- Didn't see that one coming, did you?
(Leonard:)Oh, yeah?
Well, you're not gonna see this coming.
- Aah!
- Oh, my God! Oh, my God, are you okay?
(Penny:)- What the hell do you have in there?
- My wallet, keys...
(Amy:)...and a coffee can full of change
I've been meaning to take to the bank.
- Don't move. I'll get some ice.
- Are you okay?
(Penny:)Get away from me, or I swear to God,
I will rip out what's left of your pubes.
(Leonard:)- Here.
- Oh, thanks. Aah.
(Bernadette:)Amy, you think maybe
this has gotten out of hand?
(Penny:)Gee, you think?
(Amy:)I do. Penny, Bernadette and I are sorry.
- You hit her. What did I do?
- You had my car towed.
- You were parked in Howard's spot.
- I was in Sheldon's spot.
(Bernadette:)Sheldon doesn't have a spot.
(Penny:)Guys, I think I need to go
to the emergency room.
- Okay, let's go.
- I'll drive. You can see...
(Amy:)...where the tow truck scratched my car.
- The tow truck didn't scratch your car.
- How do you know?
- Because I did it.